affilorama.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Affilorama

### Overview

_Last updated: May 24, 2018_

We respect the privacy of our customers and users. This privacy policy is designed to help you understand what personal information we gather through your use of our website, software, and services and to help you understand what Affilorama does with that information, including to whom we may disclose your personal information. Please read our privacy policy and our [Terms of Use](https://www.affilorama.com/terms). In summary, our privacy policy lets you know that:

  * We may collect personal information from you when you use this website or our software. We will not use or disclose your personal information except for purposes set out in this privacy policy or as allowed by the New Zealand Privacy Act 1993. If you are located in a jurisdiction to which the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) applies to the processing of your personal data, we will also comply with our obligations under the GDPR with respect to the processing of your personal data.
  * We may use automated tools such as cookies to collect certain information about your visit to our website. Your browser may provide you with the ability to adjust settings relating to cookies.
  * We may gather more extensive information if we are concerned about abnormal website usage patterns or security breaches.
  * We can use your information to provide you with relevant information, allow others to provide you with information, and to communicate with you, and for other purposes set out in this privacy policy.
  * We may store your personal information, and do take several steps and precautions to protect the personal information that we store.
  * If we store credit card details in accordance with this privacy policy we will delete credit card details upon request if we no longer require these details. When submitting your credit card details through our website, you may be redirected to a third party payment service provider, in which case that service provider will be responsible for maintaining the security of your credit card details.
  * You should check the privacy policies of third party websites to which this website is linked, and we are not responsible for their conduct.
  * Please feel free to email our privacy officer should you wish to access or correct personal information we hold about you. We encourage you to update any outdated billing or contact information.
  * We may change this privacy policy from time to time, including to account for new services and technologies. We recommend that you should regularly check this privacy policy for changes or updates.

#### 1\. About this privacy policy

Affilorama Group Limited values and respects the privacy of our customers and users. This privacy policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, transfer and store personal information that you provide to us. www.affilorama.com (this 'website') is operated by Affilorama Group Limited. In this privacy policy, the terms 'we', 'us', and 'our' refer to Affilorama Group Limited.

By accessing and using this website, or using our software or services, you confirm your unconditional consent to our collecting, storing, using, and disclosing your personal information in the manner set out in this privacy policy.

#### 2\. About Affilorama Group Limited

Affilorama Group Limited is a company incorporated and registered in New Zealand under company number 1870212 and NZBN 9429033841786, having its registered office c/- BDO Christchurch Limited, 287-293 Durham Street North, Christchurch 8013, New Zealand.

If you have any queries about this privacy policy, please contact us at [support@affilorama.com](mailto:support@affilorama.com) or by writing to us at PO Box 41072, Christchurch 8247, New Zealand.

#### 3\. Terms of use

Please read this privacy policy in conjunction with our [terms of use](https://www.affilorama.com/terms), which describes how you may use this website.

#### 4\. Collecting your personal information from you

We may collect the following personal information from you when you use this website or our software:

Personal information collected | When collected | Why collected  
---|---|---  
Your name and contact details | When you register to use our services or create an account with us | So that we may identify you for the purposes of entering into our terms and conditions with you, and corresponding with you  
Information regarding your business, including details of your products and stock, and your experience | When you register to use our services or create an account with us | So that we can tailor our services to your requirements  
Your username details for Clickbank | When you sign up for our affiliate programme | So that we can pay commission to you  
Your credit card details | Whenever you make a payment to us | So that we can process your payment  
Your social media details, location, and time zone | If you voluntarily provide it to us by updating your personal details | So that we can customise your use of our services and interact with you  
All personal information we collect about you, including the above | The circumstances described above, and otherwise during the course of your interaction with us | For the purposes set out in paragraph 10  
  
You may decide not to provide your personal information to us. However, if you do not provide it, we may not be able to provide you with access to certain information, services, or products, and/or customise your use of our services.

#### 5\. Collecting your personal information from third parties

We may also receive your personal information from third-party websites or services, such as Facebook, Twitter, Clickbank, and Google Analytics, whom you have authorised to disclose your personal information to us. The collection of that personal information by third parties will be governed by terms you have agreed with those third parties.

#### 6\. Automated collection

When you visit this website or use our software, we may use automated tools and methods (such as cookies, sessions, and usage monitoring software) to collect certain information about your visit or software use, including:

  1. the internet protocol address and domain name used by your computer to connect to the Internet;
  2. the operating system and the browser your computer uses, and any search engine or inbound hyperlink used to reach this website;
  3. the nature of your use of our software or services, including information you input when using our software;
  4. the date, time, and duration of your website visit; and
  5. the pages viewed by you

This information will be used in aggregate form to analyse how this website or our software is being used, for example to analyse usage patterns in order to improve this website or our software. We will not disclose any such information except in aggregate form.

#### 7\. Cookies

A “cookie” is a small piece of information sent by a server and stored on the hard drive of your computer. When you use our website, you will be asked to confirm whether you agree to our use of cookies, and if you accept we will store cookies on your computer. Cookies make it easier for you to use our site during future visits. They also allow us to monitor traffic and to personalise the content of our site for you.

This site uses the following type of cookies to provide you with certain services or functionality:

Name of cookie | Information collected | Purpose  
---|---|---  
_ga | Visits, sessions, clicks | For tracking user analytics through Google Analytics  
_gid | Visits, sessions, clicks | For tracking user analytics through Google Analytics  
_gat | Visits, sessions, clicks | For tracking user analytics through Google Analytics  
NREUM | Visits, sessions, clicks | For developers to track website performance  
JSESSIONID | Visits, sessions, clicks | For developers to track website performance  
  
Using cookies will not give us access to any data on your computer other than the data stored in the cookie. Although you may configure your web browser to not accept cookies, you may experience a loss of functionality as a result.

Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

#### 8\. Collection and deletion of credit card details

We may collect credit card details where it is necessary for the following purposes:

  1. to process the payment for which the credit card details were provided;
  2. for a subscription that requires multiple payments over time; or
  3. for your convenience (i.e., so that you can provide those details once instead of for every purchase).

You may at any time request that any of your credit card details be deleted. Please note that such deletion may cancel pending payments or subscriptions.

We use the following third party payment service providers to process credit card transactions on our behalf:

  * Braintree: https://www.braintreepayments.com
  * ClickBank: https://www.clickbank.com

Where we use third party payment service providers, you will be re-directed to a secure portal hosted by the relevant provider and you will provide your credit card details directly to that provider, in accordance with the privacy policy issued by the provider. In such cases, we will not have any access to your credit card details.

#### 9\. Additional collection

We may gather more extensive information if we are concerned, for example, about abnormal website usage patterns or security breaches.

#### 10\. Use

We will not use or disclose your personal information except as provided in this privacy policy or otherwise in accordance with the Privacy Act 1993. If you are located in a jurisdiction to which the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) applies to the processing of your personal data, we will also comply with our obligations under the GDPR with respect to the processing of your personal data.

In addition to those matters set out in clause 4 above, we may also use your personal information to:

  1. provide you with services and information that you have requested;
  2. assist our software to function;
  3. help us debug or fix software problems;
  4. provide you with support in using our software or services;
  5. provide you with important notices and information about this website and our services;
  6. provide you with other information (including promotional material, news, and event information) where you agree to receive such information;
  7. verify your identity and to assist you if you forget your username or password;
  8. improve or update this website and our products;
  9. or enhance or improve the functionality of our software, including testing new or modified functionality;
  10. respond to your enquiries and communicate with you; and
  11. personalise this website in accordance with your preferences or enhance your user experience of this website or our software.

We may also combine data or information that we have retrieved from external sources or services with personal information that we hold, for any of the above purposes.

#### 11\. Where your personal information is held

The personal information that we collect in respect of you is hosted on our behalf on servers maintained by Linode ([www.linode.com](http://www.linode.com/)), at its data centres in the United States. Linode has advised us that it will implement measures to ensure that it complies with the GDPR prior to its introduction on 25 May 2018.

We maintain a back-up of our data, including any personal information that we collect in respect of you, on servers maintained by Amazon Web Services, Inc. (‘AWS’) ([https://aws.amazon.com](https://aws.amazon.com/)), at its data centres in the United States. AWS is a participant in the EU-US Privacy Shield and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield. Further details are available [here](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_left_v4_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=202135380).

We also access and store our data, including any personal information that we collect in respect of you, through our systems and servers located at our head office in New Zealand. New Zealand is a “white list” country, the personal data protection laws of which have been assessed by the European Commission as being adequate thereby allowing transfers of personal data from the EEA to New Zealand. Transfers from Switzerland to New Zealand have also been authorised by the Swiss FDPIC.

#### 12\. Disclosure to third parties

We may share your personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys.

We may disclose your personal information to our professional advisors, contractors, service providers, business associates, related companies, and others who have agreed to treat your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy.

We may disclose your personal information to the following third parties in the context of providing services to you:

Identity of third party | Website | Reason for disclosure  
---|---|---  
Help Scout | https://www.helpscout.net | For email delivery and sending newsletters  
Smtp2go | https://www.smtp2go.com | For email delivery and sending newsletters  
Customer IO | https://customer.io | For email delivery and sending newsletters  
Webinarjam | https://www.webinarjam.com/ | Registration for webinars and interaction  
One Signal | https://onesignal.com | Sending push notifications regarding new blog posts  
Crazy Egg | https://app.crazyegg.com | For tracking visits, sessions and clicks  
Hotjar | https://insights.hotjar.com | For tracking visits, sessions and clicks  
  
#### 13\. Restrictions on use

We will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to third parties.

We will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information except:

  1. for any purpose set out in this privacy policy;
  2. where you have otherwise authorised us to do so;
  3. where we have given you notification of the intended use or disclosure and you have not objected to that use or disclosure in an anonymised form;
  4. where we believe that such use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to assist a law enforcement agency or an agency responsible for national security in the performance of their functions;
  5. where we believe that such use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to enforce any legal rights we may have, or is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of us, our users, or others; or
  6. as otherwise required or permitted by law.

#### 14\. Right to access and request correction

It is important to us that the personal information we hold about you is accurate, complete and up to date. If you are aware that this is not case and would like your personal information corrected, or simply desire access to your personal information, please contact our Privacy Officer. You may request access to your personal information that we hold. Where you make any such request:

  1. we may ask you to put your request in writing;
  2. in some circumstances permitted by law, we may not provide such information to you;
  3. where we decide not to correct or provide you with access to your personal information, we will give you our reasons for our decision;
  4. where we provide the requested information or carry out the requested correction (or where we attach to that information a statement of any correction sought but not made), we may require you to pay a reasonable fee determined by us.

#### 15\. Update information

To ensure that the contact and billing information we hold about you is accurate and current please advise us of all necessary changes to such information as soon as possible.

#### 16\. Retention period

We will hold any personal information we collect about you for as long as is necessary to provide our services to you. If you cancel your account with us, we will retain your account information unless you request that we delete it from our system. Please submit any such requests to us at [support@affilorama.com](mailto:support@affilorama.com).

#### 17\. Third party websites

This website may contain hyperlinks to websites operated by third parties. We are not responsible for the content of such websites, or the manner in which those websites collect, store, use, and distribute any personal information you provide. When you visit third party websites from hyperlinks displayed on this website, we encourage you to review the privacy statements of those websites so that you can understand how the personal information you provide may be collected, stored, used and distributed.

#### 18\. Changes to our privacy policy

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy from time to time by publishing the revised privacy policy on our website. Please check this privacy policy regularly for modifications and updates. If you continue to use this website or our software or services or if you provide any personal information after we make changes to this privacy policy, this constitutes your acceptance of those changes and the updated privacy policy.

#### 19\. Additional rights under the GDPR

In addition to the other rights granted to them under this privacy policy, EU-based users of our site may have rights under the GDPR:

  * to receive access to their personal information in a commonly-used machine-readable format;
  * to restrict processing of their personal information if a basis for doing so exists under the GDPR;
  * to have any personal information about the participant erased upon request if it is no longer relevant (the “right to be forgotten”);
  * to not be subject to a decision based solely on automated processing, including profiling;
  * to withdraw their consent to the processing of their personal data, where such consent forms the basis for the processing;
  * to lodge a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority.

Please contact our Privacy Officer using the contact details set out in this privacy policy if you wish to exercise any of these rights.
